Guide to the Urie Bronfenbrenner papers, [ca. 1960-2011]
Bronfenbrenner, Urie papers, [ca. 1960-2011]
- Series XII. Awards
  - Honorary degree from Penn State, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Nomination for National Medal of Science, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Medal-The University of the State of New York State Board of Regents (Box 33)
  - Fellow award, 1993-06-25 (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Series XIII. Biographical
  - Brief Biography of Bronfenbrenner, 2001-11-07 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Short Biography of Bronfenbrenner in German (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Biography of Urie Bronfenbrenner by Liese Bronfenbrenner, 2011 (Box 33)
  - Bibliography-Urie's, 2006; CDs-#1851 (Box 33)
  - High school records including several papers written by Urie, 1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Admissions letters, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Dissertation from the University of Michigan "Social Status, Structure, and Development in Classroom Groups", 1942 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Military Records, 1944-1949 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Academic Records, 1945-1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Personnel records, 1949-1978 (Box 3, Folder 57A)
  - Annual Reports, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Annual Reports, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Vitae of various dates (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Vitae, 1977-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vita (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - External Appointments, 1969-1979 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Memos, letters, certificates, 1963-1994 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Series XIV. Photographs
  - Russian and Chinese Children (Box 31, Folder 9-11)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photos of Urie Bronfenbrenner, 1964-1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)